SARA ELISYEVA SETIANA

Phone: +62811-2898-62

E-mail: saraelisyeva12@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/saraelisyeva

Portfolio Link:

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1Rhc6O1_DR8TwLPpmhlh_f9qmZJ

UZnuHi?usp=sharing



Drove herself to communication studies, Sara discovered her sea and dived deep into copywriting. She is experienced in crafting words for social media, campaigns, SEO, ads, and promotion services. Her strength in sailing waves comes from her adaptive and communicative energy. Get to know her to explore more adventure!

EDUCATION

Atma Jaya Yogyakarta Univeristy (2017-2022)

Faculty of Communication Science, Strategic Communication Major

Area of Interest: Corporate Communication, Customer Relation, Social Media

GPA: 3.53

EXPERIENCES

Jr. Copywriter

Glints

(August 2022-present)

- Craft all copy needs for headline, social media, ads, teaser, and campaign
- Doing copy control for all contents from stakeholders
- Created program naming: GEC Hype Club, Glint Lite Mentoring
- Collaborate with designers in crafting monthly campaigns

Copywriter Intern

(May-August 2021)

Mesta Creative, Yogyakarta

- Planed monthly content based on four content pillars of Mesta Creative
- Wrote 45 captions and 20 graphics copies for Instagram needs of Mesta Creative's Clients every month and followed the applicable deadline
- Contributed ideas for JNM Block's merchandise (2021) and participated in JNM Block 2021 Poster Exhibition
- Published "The Wrapped Labor" with the intern team as our last production



Marketing and Partnerships Intern Sadasa Academy, Yogyakarta

(July 2020-October 2020)

- Approached and made offers to potential customers
- Conducted Instagram posts and boosted 30% engagement rate in a month
- Designed campaign for Sadasa Talk #9 attended by 120 people on the webinar and boosted 100% engagement rate
- Became customer service and bridged students-mentor on class
- Maintained relationships with alumnus and customers

Student Staff of Promotion Office

(January 2018-January 2019)

Kantor Kerjasama dan Promosi UAJY, Yogyakarta

- Did research in deciding potential schools or cities for promotion needs
- Followed UAJY's quality standards in presenting Atma Jaya Yogyakarta University to several high schools in Yogyakarta, Central Java, and Ketapang
- Accomplished 30-100 registrants in every presentation and promotion
- Engaged in making Atma Jaya catalog photoshoot
- Handed events for high schools visit and training for counseling guidance teachers

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES

Public Relation (Faculty Level)

(July 2019-Augusts 2020)

BEM FISIP UAJY

- Engaged FISIP students in every event handled by BEM
- Managed partnerships with communities inside and outside of faculty
- Organized funding for natural disaster and conducted volunteers for an elementary school in Tepus

Steering Committee

(September 2019-June 2020)

CFRC (Call For Research Competition)

- Involved in recruiting process for consumption and fund venture division
- Led team to reach and monitored every division progress
- Managed evaluation program to improve performance
- Informed progress and obstacle to faculty

SKILLS

Communication Ms. Office

Teamwork Sociall Media Planning

Copywriting

Customer Service